$Addon Reconfiguration	Addon Reconfiguration
$Afflicted	Afflicted
$Bend Player schlong	Bend Player schlong
$Bend schlong down	Bend schlong down
$Bend schlong up	Bend schlong up
$Both	Both
$Campy	Campy
$Change	Change
$Clean	Clean
$Clean schlongified armors{}	Clean schlongified armors ({})
$Cleaned armors{}	Cleaned {} schlongified armors
$Display SOS notifications	Display SOS notifications
$General Settings	General Settings
$Global Settings	Global Settings
$Equipped armor{}	Equipped armor: {}
$Female	Female
$Gender options	Gender options
$hl_addon_clean	Removes this schlong from all people that currently have it.\nThis means the next time you encounter them they will have a new schlong randomly assigned.
$hl_addon_probability	This resets the probability that this schlong is used for all races of this addon to the selected value.\nYou can finetune the race specific settings after you have set your overall preference for this addon here.\nDefault: 10
$hl_addon_race	Allow this schlong for that race
$hl_addon_race_probability	Relative probability this schlong will be selected for that race.\n0 = not gona happen | 100 = very likely\nrelative: means that the final outcome also depends on the probability that other addons have assigned for that race.
$hl_addon_race_size	Size distribution of this schlong for that race.\n -100 = all small | 0 = equal distribution | 100 = all big
$hl_addon_remove	Completely remove references to this schlong addon.\nWARNING: After using remove, save the game then exit and delete the addon esp, reload the saved game and resave it again.
$hl_addon_size	This resets the schlong size distribution of all races of this addon to the selected value.\nYou can finetune the race specific settings after you have set your overall preference for this addon here.\nDefault: 0
$hl_armor_revealing	Toggles currently equipped Body Armor as Revealing or not.\nNote: this affects all copies of the armor, both male and female
$hl_bend_down	Use this key to bend the schlong of the targeted NPC down (if he has any).\nDefault: Page Down
$hl_bend_player	Use this key together with the configured up/down keys to bend the schlong of the Player (if he has any).\nDefault: Left Shift
$hl_bend_up	Use this key to bend the schlong of the targeted NPC up (if he has any).\nDefault: Page Up
$hl_clean_armors	Reverts all schlongified, non-vanilla armors to their original state
$hl_debug_spells	Get SOS internal status information for this character.\nThis information can be used in bug reports to help us understand what might be going wrong.
$hl_erection_spells	Add or remove Spells that can control schlongs erections
$hl_gender_options	This schlong is multi-gender and is distributed to both men and women. Here you can restrict it to a single genre.\nNote: changing this option does not remove the schlong from the characters who already have it
$hl_global_boost	With this option you can boost the size of schlongs. Usually SOS addons will come with a maximum size that is somewhat still believable.\nBoost it to insanity or reduce it to whatever you think is appropriate\nDefault: 0%
$hl_global_size	This resets the schlong size distribution of all addons for all races to the selected value.\nYou can finetune the addon and race specific settings after you have set your overall preference here.\nDefault: 0
$hl_global_type	This resets the probability that a specific schlong type is used for all addons for all races to the selected value.\nYou can finetune the addon and race specific settings after you have set your overall preference here.\nDefault: 10
$hl_min_size	Minimum value of the size of schlongs. NPCs get a random size, as configured in each addon's specific settings.\nDefault: 4
$hl_max_size	Maximum value of the size of schlongs. NPCs get a random size, as configured in each addon's specific settings.\nDefault: 10
$hl_no_npc	Move the cursor over the NPC until you see the 'E' activate/Dialogue option. Then open the MCM menu
$hl_notifications_enabled	Hide or show SOS messages in the top-left corner of the screen
$hl_npc_schlong	Change the schlong of the targeted NPC. Close the MCM menu to see the changes
$hl_npc_size	Change the schlong size of the targeted NPC
$hl_player_schlong	Change the schlong of this character. Close the MCM menu to see the changes.\n(*): Schlong not available for this character's race and/or gender
$hl_player_size	Change the schlong size of your character
$hl_potions_enabled	Uncheck to stop falmers and dragons from dropping SOS size potions. It may take a while until the change takes effect.
$hl_remove_SOS	Completely removes all SOS references. WARNING: After using remove, save the game then exit, uninstall all SOS mods, reload the saved game and resave it again.
$hl_restart	Restarts all schlong mods and SOS scripts
$hl_schlongification_enabled	Schlongification is the proccess that allows the assignment of schlong shape/sizes to new NPCs.\n Disabling it will cause this proccess to stop, but will allow the playerto complete brawling quests.
$Key bindings	Key bindings
$Male	Male
$Max schlong size	Max schlong size
$Min schlong size	Min schlong size
$missing_schlong	<Missing schlong>
$Mod management	Mod management
$Name{}	Name: {}
$None	None
$No NPC selected	No NPC selected
$No schlong	No schlong
$No SOS skeleton	No SOS compatible skeleton
$NPC Dialogs	NPC Dialogs
$NPC Settings	NPC Settings
$NPC size distribution	NPC schlong size distribution
$NPC size probability	NPC schlong size probability
$NPC type probability	NPC schlong type probability
$Off	Off
$Player NPC Settings	Player / NPC Settings
$Player Settings	Player Settings
$RacenameVampire{}	{} Vampire
$Remove	Remove
$Remove SOS	Remove SOS
$Restart SOS	Restart SOS
$Revealing	Revealing
$Revealing (built-in)	Revealing (built-in)
$Schlongify nearby NPCs	Schlongify nearby NPCs
$Schlong size	Schlong size
$Schlong size multiplier	Schlong size multiplier
$Shape Probability	Shape Probability
$Size Probability	Size Probability
$SOS first time	SOS: first time initialization complete
$SOS internal information	SOS internal information
$SOS potions	SOS potions
$SOS update complete	SOS: update complete
$Spells erections	Spells to control erections
$Spells internals	Spells to check SOS internals
$Vanilla	Vanilla
$warn_clean_addon_1	Do you really want to take this schlong away from all people?
$warn_clean_addon_2{}	Removed this schlong from {} people
$warn_custom_actor	This Actor was not designed to work with this shape addon or its a custom race! Are you sure you want to Schlongify this Actor?
$warn_keybinding{}{}	New keybinding has a potential conflict with: {}-{}\nChange keybinding anyway?
$warn_remove_addon_1	Do you really want to try to remove everything added by this addon?
$warn_remove_addon_2{}	Next steps you need to do:\n1. Save game and exit\n2. Uninstall "{}"\n3. Reload the save and wait for a while\n4. Overwrite save again
$warn_remove_SOS_1	Do you really want to remove SOS?
$warn_remove_SOS_2	Next steps you need to do:\n1. Save game and exit\n2. Uninstall all SOS mods\n3. Reload the save and wait for a while\n4. Overwrite save again
$warn_reschlongify{}	After pressing {} please wait for the reschlongification to finish
$warn_restart_SOS	Do you really want to restart SOS?
